todo
[ ] create faq list
[ ] create fake advice
[ ] create template from home html page
[ ] create favorite button for advice
[ ] Create HTML template for all pages; include all relevant outside source links and scripts
[ ] Create login/signup forms
[ ] create give advice page
[ ] Include login verification
[ ] Create SCSS file and CSS file; link together
[x ] Create JS file
[x ] API - Unsplash for background photos
[ ] API - Wunderground for weather info



